#This folder contains the Octave codes to perform the Movable Type Heatmap Docking. This code should be run following the generation of the streptavidin conformations with the flexible loop3−4 region using the MTflexb.

#Before running the Movable Type Heatmap Docking code, users need to convert the conformations from the file cond_all.netcdf provided in the directory \Strept_code_conf_gen_with_AllOutputConformations\output_structures\ to individual pdb files using proper #utilities e.g. CPPTRAJ, and put all these protein pdb files and the input ligand mol2 file (using SYBYL atom type), which is provided in the directory \Strept_code_conf_gen_with_AllOutputConformations\Input_structures\, in the same folder.

#Run the executable file DOCKING_EXE_file.m in a matlab/octave compiler to perfrom the Movable Type Heatmap Docking. The user need to enter in this file (1) the directory for the aforementioned input structure files (the protein conformer pdb files and the #ligand input mol2 file) within the single quotation marks in line 2 "home_dir = strcat('input structure file directory\');" and (2) the output directory that the users want to restore the ligand docking poses. Backslash signs are necessary in the end when #entering both directories.

#Docked poses outputs generated from the authors can be downloaded from the corresponding folder using the provided Dropbox link.